homeclips.com 2019-12-14

# HomeClips - Privacy Policy

This document details important information regarding the use and disclosure of User Data collected on HomeClips.com   
The security of your Data is very important to us, and as such we take all appropriate steps to limit the risk that it may be lost, damaged or misused.   
This site expressly and strictly limits its membership and/or viewing privileges to adults 18 years of age and over or having attained the age of majority in their community. All persons who do not meet its criteria are strictly forbidden from accessing or viewing the contents of this Site. We do not knowingly seek or collect any personal information or data from persons who have not attained the age of majority. We are committed to protecting your privacy. We use the information we collect about you and your payment method to process transactions only. Private account and address information is necessary to verify that you are the person making the purchase and to thwart potential fraud. All information gathered in the course of a transaction is transmitted securely and is protected by our database throughout the transaction process. By visiting our website or otherwise interacting with network, you agreed to accept the practices described in this Privacy Statement. 

WE WILL NEVER PROVIDE YOUR INFORMATION TO ANOTHER PARTY AND WE WILL NEVER SOLICIT YOU. 

Please read on for more details about our privacy statement.

## 1\. What information do we collect? How do we use it?

When you register, we need to know your name, e-mail address, Internet Protocol ("IP") address, mailing address, phone number and payment information. This allows us to safely process and fulfill your purchase process, as well as to notify you of your delivery status. We log the IP address for address verification purposes. However, the "IP" address is never used for any other purpose than to process your purchase. 

WE ONLY USE THE INFORMATION TO PROCESS, CONFIRM AND NOTIFY YOU OF THE SPECIFIC PURCHASE YOU ARE MAKING.

## 2\. How does HomeClips protect customer information?

When you purchase a product with us, we use an internal secure network. This network encrypts all information between the servers of HomeClips. Furthermore, all of the customer data we collect is protected against unauthorized access.

## 3\. What about "cookies"?

"Cookies" are small pieces of information that are stored by your browser on your computer's hard drive. Our cookies do not contain any personally identifying information, but they do enable us to provide features such as linking and reselling. Most Web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually change your browser to prevent that. Sometimes at HomeClips we do use cookies during the purchase process, to have your own PC remember what kind of information was entered. We collect this information to better develop a sense of what services our customers need and not to track your individual usage patterns.

## 4\. Correct/Update of Information

You may access, correct and update your personal information by contacting us.

## 5\. Disclosure to Third Parties

HomeClips does not sell, disclose or provide personal information to third parties. 

WE NEVER PROVIDE PERSONAL CREDIT CARD, DEBIT CARD OR BANKING INFORMATION.

## 6\. How will HomeClips correspond with me?

HomeClips will notify consumers via email that their purchase is completed. From time to time we may use your personal information to contact you by email concerning your use of our services. These communications are intended to inform you of important information regarding your account or about general services provided by us. Only in rare circumstances will HomeClips contact consumers via telephone to confirm purchase or resolve disputes.

## 7\. Will HomeClips notify me to changes in the way it uses Personally Identifiable Information?

Should HomeClips make material changes to our Privacy Statement and method in which we handle your Personally Identifiable Information, we will notify you via email. Should you wish to cancel your account or affiliation, you will be able to do so by responding to HomeClips. If you have any concern about privacy at HomeClips, please contact us and we will attempt to assist you. Because our business and the online business is fluid and changes constantly, this Privacy Statement may change as well. You are advised to check our website to keep apprised of any recent changes. 

WE WILL NOT INCLUDE PERSONALLY IDENTIFYING INFORMATION. 

HomeClips may release account information when we believe, in good faith, that such release is reasonably necessary to (i) enforce or apply the terms of any of our user agreements; (ii) protect the rights, property or safety of HomeClips, our users, or others or (iii) comply with any legal requirement to disclose such information to any local, state, federal, national or international governmental enforcement authorities. Although we are committed to the strongest possible protection of your privacy, certain other websites may not be. Therefore, we shall not be responsible for the content or privacy policies of other websites such as those of advertisers to which it may link. Our Privacy Statement is only applicable to the information we collect on the HomeClips website. You should review the privacy policy of every online service you use before submitting personal or otherwise private inform ation. In summary, we are committed to protecting your privacy. We do not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. By using our Web site, you consent to the collection and use of this information by HomeClips. If we decide to change our privacy statement, we will post those changes on this page so that you are always aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances we disclose it.
